▍2026 蒙特利尔 ATP1000 第二轮
商竣程 7-5 4-6 7-6(5) 卢布列夫 · 赛后场上采访
Well, Jerry congratulations after you came
杰瑞 恭喜你
over to the bench. You just dropped
刚才你回到座位那会儿
your head and kind of stared at the court
低着头 盯着球场
for a little while. What's going
看了好一阵子
through your mind after two hours
打完这两小时 45 分钟
and 45 minutes of that?
你脑子里在想什么？
Well, I think first of all,
嗯 首先我想说
Andrey is a great friend.
安德烈是很好的朋友
He's a great competitor, a good champion
他是很强的对手 也是位好冠军
on the courts, and it's a pleasure
能在球场上再一次
to share the court with him again
跟他同场 是件愉快的事
since since last time we played
上一次 上一次我们交手
in Hong Kong,
还是在香港
but more happily, I'm healthy.
但更让我高兴的是 我健康了
I'm 100% playing my best tennis
我百分百打出了最好的网球
and just really happy
也真的很开心
to be in Montreal playing healthy
能来到蒙特利尔 身体健康
and playing happy again
重新打得开心
What does a win like
这样一场胜利
that do for you do for your confidence?
对你意味着什么 对信心呢？
And what does it tell you
它又能告诉你什么
about what your level is right now?
关于你现在处在什么水平？
Well, I think I know the tennis is there
嗯 我知道 我的网球还在那儿
but I just have to have to get it out of me
只是得 得把它从身体里打出来
and stay healthy. But again,
还要保持健康 不过话说回来
that's the that's the biggest part
这就是 这就是最关键的一点
about being a top player. Andrey, Andrey, he
想成为顶尖球员 安德烈 安德烈
has that and he's competing all year.
他做到了 而且他全年都在打
So that's something
所以这一点
that I have to learn from the top players
是我得向顶尖球员学的东西
to get my level back. Just again super happy
好把状态找回来 再说一次
to be healthy.
我真的很高兴自己健康
That's the number one priority
这是第一位的事
and if I can win some matches,
如果还能赢下几场球
that'll be amazing too
那就再好不过了
Jerry.
杰瑞
Thanks so much.
非常感谢
Thank you
谢谢